{"data":[{"question":"When the moon ___, we went to bed.","a":"raised","b":"rose","c":"had been risen","d":"was raised","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Rise: (sun\/moon\/star) to appear in the sky \n- Simple past tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"How much do these cards ___?","a":"cost","b":"pay","c":"take","d":"spend","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Cost: to have a particular price","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"I ___ one hundred dollars for the used bike.","a":"spent","b":"cost","c":"paid","d":"used","answer":"3","explain":"\n-Pay: to give someone money for something you buy or for a service","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"My parents and I are going to ___ my uncle at the station tomorrow.","a":"accept","b":"receive","c":"welcome","d":"meet","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Meet:to go to a place where someone will be at a particular time, according to an arrangement, so that you can talk or do something together","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Can you _________ me the book which you ___ from the school library?","a":"borrow, lent","b":"borrow, lend","c":"lend, borrowed","d":"lent, borrowed","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Lend:to let someone borrow money or something that belongs to you for a short time\n- Borrow:to use something that belongs to someone else and that you must give back to them later","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"The official ___ bribes from a citizen, but he refused to ___ it.","a":"took, accept","b":"received, take","c":"accepted, receive","d":"took, receive","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Accept\/take a bribe: money or a gift that you illegally give someone to persuade them to do something for you","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Bob ___ that he had gained the singer's autograph.","a":"hopes","b":"wanted","c":"demanded","d":"wished","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Wish: if you wish to do something or you wish to have it done for you, you want to do it or want to have it done","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"An idea suddenly ___ me.","a":"happened to","b":"beat","c":"came","d":"struck","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Struck: if something strikes you, you think of it, notice it, or realize that it is important, interesting, true etc","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"Working with a computer ___ great care.","a":"orders","b":"requires","c":"wants","d":"asks","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Require: to need something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"},{"question":"The police ___ everywhere for the missing bracelet.","a":"found","b":"looked","c":"noticed","d":"searched","answer":"4","explain":"- Search: to try to find something or someone by looking carefully\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"18","type":"1"}]}